Hi, Joey.
嗨，喬伊。
How'd the audition go?
試鏡怎麼樣？
Incredible.
極好的。
I met the director this time, and you will never believe who it
這次見到了導演，你絕對不會相信他是誰
was.
曾是。
Who?
WHO？
All right, I'll give you one hint.
好吧，我給你一個提示。
Warren Beatty.
沃倫·比蒂。
Wow!
哇！
Yeah, there's just one thing that might be kind of a problem.
是的，只有一件事可能有點問題。
See, I, uh, I had to kiss this guy.
看，我，呃，我必須親吻這傢伙。
Because he was just so darn cute?
因為他實在太可愛了？
No, as part of the audition.
不，作為試鏡的一部分。
See, I'm up for the part of this guy whom the main guy
瞧，我很喜歡這個人的角色，他是主角
kisses.
親吻。
Well, hey, you're an actor.
嗯，嘿，你是個演員。
I see you just suck it up and you do it.
我看到你只是忍氣吞聲，然後就這麼做了。
Or you just do it.
或者你就這麼做。
I did do it.
我確實做到了。
I'm a professional.
我是專業人士。
Besides, my first girlfriend was Lisa DiBattista, so I'm no stranger to the
此外，我的第一個女朋友是麗莎·迪巴蒂斯塔（Lisa DiBattista），所以我對
mustache.
鬍子。
So what's the problem?
那麼問題出在哪裡呢？
See, after the scene, Mr. Beatty comes up to me and he says,
瞧，這場戲結束後，比蒂先生走到我面前說：
Good actor, bad kisser.
好演員，壞接吻者。
Can you believe that?
你能相信嗎？
Me?
我？
Not a good kisser?
接吻技巧不太好？
That's like, like Mother Teresa.
就像德蕾莎修女一樣。
Not a good mother.
不是一個好母親。
Oh, come on.
哦，來吧。
Who cares what that guy thinks?
誰在乎那傢伙怎麼想？
You know, what does Warren Beatty know about kissing?
你知道華倫比蒂對接吻瞭解多少嗎？
Oh.
哦。
Love loves you anyway It's like you're always stuck in second gear And
無論如何愛都愛你就像你總是被困在第二檔並且
when it hasn't been your day or week or month Then all you
當這不是你的一天、一週或一個月，那麼你所有人
hear was I'll be there for you When the rain starts to pour
聽說當雨開始傾盆大雨時我會在你身邊
I'll be there for you When the heavy rain starts to pour I'll
我會在你身邊當大雨傾盆而下時我會
be there for you When
在你身邊的時候
the heavy rain starts to pour Hey, what did your agent say?
大雨開始傾盆而下 嘿，你的經紀人怎麼說？
Yep, this kiss thing is definitely a problem.
是的，這個接吻的事情肯定是有問題的。
Mr. Beatty wants to see it again on Monday.
比蒂先生想週一再看一次。
Man, I gotta figure out what I'm doing wrong.
夥計，我得弄清楚我做錯了什麼。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
Uh, one of you girls come over here and kiss me.
呃，你們中的一個女孩過來吻我。
Forget it!
忘了它！
Hey, come on.
嘿，來吧。
I need your help here.
我這裡需要你的幫忙。
All right, I'll do it.
好吧，我會做的。
I've kissed him before.
我以前吻過他。
I can do it again.
我可以再做一次。
See this?
看到這個了嗎？
Huh?
啊？
This is a friend.
這是一個朋友。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Let's go.
我們走吧。
All right.
好的。
I'm done.
我受夠了。
Okay.
好的。
Very good.
非常好。
Firm but tender.
堅定但溫柔。
I'd recommend you to a friend.
我會把你推薦給朋友。
Then I don't know what it is.
然後我就不知道那是什麼了。
What's the problem?
有什麼問題嗎？
Jerry, you know, maybe you're just not used to kissing men.
傑瑞，你知道，也許你只是不習慣親吻男人。
You know, maybe you just tensed up a little bit.
你知道，也許你只是有點緊張。
Maybe that's what you need to work on.
也許這就是你需要努力的地方。
Yeah, that makes sense.
是的，這是有道理的。
Over my dead body.
在我的屍體上。
And I'll be using his dead body as a shield.
我會用他的屍體當盾牌。
Come on out, honey.
出來吧，親愛的。
I'm telling you, you look good.
我告訴你，你看起來不錯。
Tell her she looks good.
告訴她她看起來不錯。
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
I cannot believe I had to walk down the aisle in front of
我不敢相信我必須走在前面的走道上
200 people looking like something you drink when you're nauseous.
200個人看起來就像你噁心時喝的東西。
So don't.
所以不要。
I don't see why we have to go to this thing anyway.
我不明白為什麼我們一定要去做這件事。
It's your ex-fiancee's wedding.
這是你前未婚妻的婚禮。
Because I promised Mindy I would.
因為我答應明迪我會的。
Yeah, well, you promised Barry you'd marry him.
是的，好吧，你答應巴里你會嫁給他。
Look, you guys, I have to go.
聽著，你們，我得走了。
I'm a maid of honor.
我是一名伴娘。
Besides, you know what?
除此之外，你知道嗎？
I just need to be in a room again with these people and
我只需要再次和這些人待在一個房間裡
feel good about myself.
我自我感覺良好。
Boo!
噓！
Someone's wearing the same clothes they had on last night.
有人穿著昨晚穿的衣服。
Did someone get a little action?
有人有一點行動嗎？
I may have.
我可能有。
Woo-hoo!
嗚呼！
It's done.
完成了。
What's she look like?
她長什麼樣子？
Well, we haven't actually met.
嗯，其實我們還沒見過面。
We just stayed up all night talking on the Internet.
我們就這樣徹夜不眠地在網路上聊天。
Woo-hoo!
嗚呼！
Geek!
極客！
I like this girl, okay?
我喜歡這個女孩，可以嗎？
I seriously like this girl.
我真的很喜歡這個女孩。
You know how sometimes I tend to get a little defended and quippy?
你知道有時我會變得有點辯護和俏皮嗎？
Get out.
出去。
Well, she totally called me on it, okay?
好吧，她完全打電話給我了，好嗎？
She said, cut it out, get real, and I did.
她說，別再這樣了，面對現實，我就這麼做了。
Wow.
哇。
What's that like?
那是什麼樣子的？
Just like this.
就像這樣。
Me.
我。
No jokes.
沒有笑話。
All right, stop it.
好吧，別說了。
You're freaking me out.
你嚇壞我了。
Yeah, I don't like you this way.
是的，我不喜歡你這樣。
All right, I'll see you guys later.
好吧，我們稍後見。
Bye, Richard.
再見，理查德。
Bye-bye.
再見。
Bye, sweetie.
再見，親愛的。
I love you.
我愛你。
I love you, too.
我也愛你。
I think my boyfriend's ever so dreamy.
我覺得我男友真是太有夢想了。
I wonder what our wedding's gonna be like.
我想知道我們的婚禮會是什麼樣子。
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼？
What wedding?
什麼婚禮？
Come on, like you never talk about that?
來吧，就像你從不談論這個一樣？
No, never.
不，從來沒有。
I mean, we're just living in the moment.
我的意思是，我們只是活在當下。
God, it is so nice for Moritz not to get all hung up
天哪，莫里茲沒有結束通話電話真是太好了
on where's this going.
這到底是怎麼回事。
Afraid to ask him?
不敢問他？
Could not be more terrified.
不能更害怕了。
Well, I think you should seriously consider the marriage thing.
嗯，我覺得你應該認真考慮一下婚姻的事情。
Give Rachel another chance to dress up like Princess Bubble-Yum.
再給瑞秋一次裝扮成泡泡糖公主的機會。
I was laughing at this quip Leno made last night.
我被萊諾昨晚說的俏皮話逗笑了。
I wasn't laughing at your dress.
我沒有笑你的衣服。
I love you.
我愛你。
Where's Vinny?
維尼在哪裡？
There he is.
他就在那裡。
Where's Vinny?
維尼在哪裡？
There he is.
他就在那裡。
Oh, you know, that's probably why babies learn to talk, so they can
哦，你知道，這可能是嬰兒學習說話的原因，這樣他們就可以
tell grown-ups to cut it out.
告訴大人把它剪掉。
Hey, you know, I got a question for you.
嘿，你知道，我有個問題想問你。
Just a little thing, no pressure.
一點小事，沒有壓力。
Okay.
好的。
Do you ever, um, like, think about the future?
你有沒有想過未來？
Sure, I do.
當然，我願意。
Yeah?
是的？
Am I in it?
我在其中嗎？
Honey, you are it.
親愛的，你就是它。
Oh, God, you're about to get so lucky.
噢，天哪，你的運氣真好。
Yeah?
是的？
Keep talking.
繼續說話。
Well, um, sometimes I think about selling my practice.
嗯，有時我會考慮出售我的診所。
We could move to France, make French toast.
我們可以搬到法國，做法式吐司。
Okay, so, um, we're in France, and, uh, we're making the toast.
好吧，嗯，我們在法國，而且，呃，我們正在烤麵包。
Do you see a little bassinet in the corner?
你看到角落有個小搖籃了嗎？
Like a hound?
像獵犬一樣？
Not a basset.
不是巴塞特。
A bassinet.
一個搖籃。
You really need the bassinet?
你真的需要搖籃嗎？
Well, I just think the baby would keep falling off the dog.
嗯，我只是覺得孩子會一直從狗身上掉下來。
Do you, um, do you not see kids in our future?
你，嗯，你看不到我們未來的孩子嗎？
Oh, hey, I love children.
哦，嘿，我喜歡孩子。
I have children.
我有孩子。
But I just don't want to be 70 when our kids go off
但我只是不想等到 70 歲的時候我們的孩子就離開了
to college and our life can finally start.
上了大學，我們的生活終於可以開始了。
Look, I want you now.
聽著，我現在就想要你。
That's great.
那太棒了。
You know, we don't need to talk about this now.
你知道，我們現在不需要談論這個。
Really, I mean, this is so, like, way, way, way in the future.
真的，我的意思是，這就是未來的方式。
I'm talking hovercrafts and apes taking over the planet.
我說的是氣墊船和猿猴接管地球。
Come on, Chandler, I want this part so much.
來吧，錢德勒，我非常想要這個部分。
Just one kiss, I won't tell him.
就一個吻，我不會告訴他。
Joey, no means no.
喬伊，不就是不。
I'm sorry, we don't have your sheep.
抱歉，我們沒有你的羊。
Oh, Rich, I think you look cute.
哦，裡奇，我覺得你看起來很可愛。
And you, huh, you, you like to eat with a spoon.
還有你，呵呵，你，你喜歡用湯匙吃飯。
Get away from me, I said no!
離我遠點，我說了不！
Richard Buzz is waiting downstairs.
理查德·巴茲正在樓下等著。
Oh, Richard's here?
噢，理查德來了？
I should run down and say goodbye to him.
我應該跑下去跟他告別。
Bye.
再見。
Good luck.
祝你好運。
So, how's your date with your cyber chick going?
那麼，你和你的網路小妞的約會進行得怎麼樣了？
Oh, hey, what is all that?
哦，嘿，那是什麼？
Oh, it's a website, it's the Guggenheim Museum.
哦，這是一個網站，這是古根漢美術館。
See, she likes art and I like funny words.
看，她喜歡藝術，而我喜歡有趣的文字。
What does she mean by HH?
她說的HH是什麼意思？
It means we're holding hands.
這意味著我們手牽著手。
Are you the cutest?
你是最可愛的嗎？
I'm afraid I might just be.
恐怕我可能就是這樣。
You know what I think is so great, that you're totally into this
你知道我認為這太棒了，你完全投入其中
person, yet for all you know, she could be like 90 years old
一個人，但據你所知，她可能已經90歲了
or have two heads or...
或有兩個頭或...
It could be a guy.
這可能是個男人。
Hey, it's not a guy, all right?
嘿，這不是一個男人，好嗎？
I know her.
我認識她。
It could be like a big, giant guy.
它可能就像一個巨大的傢伙。
Man, I got this close to him and Monica need me in the
夥計，我離他這麼近，莫妮卡需要我
back.
後退。
What's going on?
這是怎麼回事？
We were just wondering if Chandler's girlfriend's a girl.
我們只是想知道錢德勒的女朋友是不是女孩。
Oh, just ask her how long she's gonna live.
哦，問她還能活多久。
Women live longer than men.
女性比男性壽命更長。
How do you not fall down more?
怎樣才能不摔倒更多呢？
Okay, ask her what is her current method of birth control.
好的，問問她目前的節育方法是什麼。
All right.
好的。
My husband is sleeping with his secretary.
我丈夫正在和他的秘書睡覺。
She's married?
她結婚了？
Well, at least we know she's a woman.
好吧，至少我們知道她是個女人。
I can't believe she's married.
我不敢相信她已經結婚了。
Oh, man, I'm sorry.
哦，夥計，對不起。
This must be really tough for you, huh?
這對你來說一定很難吧？
So, I read this article the other day that says you're not supposed
所以，我前幾天讀過這篇文章，說你不應該
to throw rice at weddings because when pigeons eat rice, it kills them.
在婚禮上扔大米，因為當鴿子吃大米時，就會殺死它們。
Oh, so that's why you never see pigeons in sushi bars.
哦，這就是為什麼你在壽司店裡從來沒有看到鴿子的原因。
See, we're having fun.
看，我們玩得很開心。
Oh, absolutely.
哦，絕對是。
Yeah, you know, I'm not even thinking about that thing that we're not
是的，你知道，我什至沒有想到我們沒有想到的事情
gonna be thinking about.
會思考。
Neither am I.
我也不是。
Hey there.
嘿。
Hi.
你好。
Are you all right?
你還好嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
When I was in the bathroom, I saw the window that I crawled
當我在浴室裡時，我看到了我爬過的窗戶
out of at my wedding and, God, I just started thinking I shouldn't
在我的婚禮上，上帝，我開始想我不應該
be here, you know?
就在這裡，你知道嗎？
I shouldn't.
我不應該。
People are gonna be looking at me and judging me and thinking about
人們會看著我、評斷我、思考我
the last time.
最後一次。
Sweetie, it's gonna be okay, all right?
親愛的，一切都會好起來的，好嗎？
It's a wedding.
這是一場婚禮。
Generally, people focus on the bride.
一般來說，人們的注意力都集中在新娘身上。
God, I know you're right.
天哪，我知道你是對的。
All righty.
好吧。
Everybody look at me.
大家都看著我。
Good, all right.
很好，好吧。
It's time.
是時候了。
Bridesmaids and ushers, let's say two lines.
伴娘和引座員，我們說兩行。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Okay, I'll see you after the thing.
好的，事情結束後見。
Okay, good luck.
好的，祝你好運。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Okay.
好的。
Ah.
啊。
God, why the hell didn't you tell me?
天哪，你為什麼不告訴我？
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉。
What was I supposed to do, stand up and shout, Hey, Rachel, your
我該怎麼辦，站起來喊，嘿，雷切爾，你的
buddy's showing.
朋友的表現。
Yeah, better you than Barry's uncle.
是的，你比巴里的叔叔更好。
Oh, my God, this is so humiliating.
天哪，這太丟臉了。
I think the only thing that tops that one was when I was
我認為唯一最重要的是當我
in eighth grade and I had to sing the Copacabana in front of
八年級時我必須在同學面前唱科帕卡巴納曲
the entire school.
整個學校。
I think I got two lines into it before I ran and freaked
我想在我跑過去嚇壞之前我已經寫了兩行了
out.
出去。
Oh, my God, my entire life's flashing before my eyes.
天哪，我的一生都在我眼前閃現。
Rachel, hey, look, I remember that.
雷切爾，嘿，聽著，我記得。
It wasn't so bad.
情況並沒有那麼糟。
Oh, Rosswood, just stop.
哦，羅斯伍德，停下來。
You got me.
你抓住了我。
I'm dating you.
我正在和你約會。
Rachel.
雷切爾。
Oh, hi, Mr. Weinberg.
哦，嗨，溫伯格先生。
Hi, Mrs. Weinberg.
你好，溫伯格太太。
It's so wonderful to see you again, my dear.
很高興再次見到你，親愛的。
In fact, I hardly expected to see so much.
事實上，我沒想到會看到這麼多。
You told me you didn't see anything.
你告訴我你什麼也沒看到。
I tell you a lot of things.
我告訴你很多事情。
Well, it's wonderful to have you up and about again, dear.
Stay well.
保持健康。
Okay, now that is the third time someone has said something like that
to me today.
今天對我來說。
Rach?
瑞秋？
Oh, hi.
哦，嗨。
Oh, my God, I'm married.
天哪，我結婚了。
I'm Mrs. Dr. Barry Hunter-Farber.
我是巴里‧亨特-法伯博士夫人。
I'm so proud of you men.
我為你們感到驕傲。
Men?
男人？
Oh, Rach.
哦，瑞秋。
Still here.
還在這裡。
At our wedding, they were packing up the chopped liver about now.
Yeah, I love that story.
是的，我喜歡那個故事。
I have a question for you guys.
我有一個問題想問你們。
Why do people keep saying it's good to see me up and about?
Well, after you ran out on your wedding, Barry's parents told people you
were sort of insane.
有點瘋狂。
Insane?
瘋狂的？
From the syphilis.
來自梅毒。
What?
什麼？
What are they going to say?
他們會說什麼？
You didn't love me anymore?
你不再愛我了嗎？
Come on.
快點。
Your choices were that or syphilis?
你的選擇是那個還是梅毒？
Hey, sweetie, at least this puts your whole tushy show into perspective.
Angela?
安吉拉？
Joey Tribbiani.
喬伊·崔比亞尼。
Listen, uh, what are you doing tonight?
聽著，呃，你今晚要做什麼？
I know you're seeing that guy.
我知道你正在見那個人。
I was thinking maybe you could bring him.
我在想也許你可以帶他來。
Hello?
你好？
Aren't you going to answer her?
你不打算回答她嗎？
That's like the 10th bing-bong message she sent.
這就像她傳送的第十條「冰棒」訊息。
She wants to know what's wrong.
她想知道出了什麼問題。
What's wrong?
怎麼了？
You're married.
你結婚了。
That's what's wrong.
這就是問題所在。
Oh, my.
哦，我的。
What?
什麼？
She wants to meet you in person.
她想親自見到你。
Hey, look, Phoebe, I wanted to meet her in person, too, okay?
嘿，聽著，菲比，我也想親自見見她，好嗎？
But she's married.
但她已經結婚了。
She has a husband.
她有一個丈夫。
What if the husband person is the wrong guy and you are the
如果老公選錯了人，而你就是那個人怎麼辦？
right guy?
對的人嗎？
You don't get chances like this all the time.
你不會一直有這樣的機會。
If you don't meet her now, you're going to be kicking yourself when
如果你現在沒有見到她，到時候你會後悔的
you're 80, which is hard to do, and that's how you break a
你已經80歲了，這很難做到，這就是你如何打破
hip.
時髦的。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Listen to that.
聽聽那個。
Those are the bing-bongs of a woman in love with you.
這些都是愛你的女人們的叮噹聲。
Okay.
好的。
I'll do it.
我會做的。
Oh, yay!
哦，耶！
Okay, great.
好的，太好了。
Now go put on your shoes and then march out there and meet
現在穿上你的鞋子，然後出發去見
her.
她。
Oh, my God, no!
哦，天哪，不！
Wait, you have to take a shower, because, ew, and I'll get the...
等等，你得去洗個澡，因為，呃，我去拿…
No, you have to answer her.
不行，你必須回答她。
Answer her first.
先回答她吧。
No, no, you know what?
不，不，你知道嗎？
Make some coffee, because it's too much.
煮點咖啡吧，因為太多了。
Okay, one more, please.
好的，請再來一張。
Come on, I'm going to get it in this time, I will.
Okay, last chance.
好吧，最後一次機會。
Again, I'm sorry.
再次抱歉。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
Maybe I don't need to have children.
也許我不需要孩子。
You know, maybe I just think I do, because that's what society...
And by that, I mean my mom.
我指的是我的媽媽。
My mom has always convinced me that I...
我媽媽一直讓我相信我...
I do.
我願意。
I have to have children.
我必須要孩子。
I'm sorry, I just do.
對不起，我只是這麼做。
Yo, can I have your attention, please?
喲，請注意一下好嗎？
Best man making a toast here.
伴郎在這裡祝酒。
Thank you.
謝謝。
I remember when Barry got home from his first date with Rachel.
我記得巴里第一次與瑞秋約會回家時。
Huh?
啊？
What?
什麼？
You hired the same band.
你們僱用了同一個樂團。
I can't use the same speech?
我不能使用相同的語音嗎？
Thank you.
謝謝。
Thank you very much.
非常感謝。
Anyway, I wish you both a wonderful life together.
不管怎樣，我祝福你們倆共同度過美好的生活。
Aw.
噢。
And Rachel.
還有雷切爾。
What?
什麼？
No, no, no, in all seriousness, there's not a lot of women who
不不不，說實話，沒有多少女人能做到這一點
would have had the guts to come back here tonight, and even fewer
今晚有勇氣回到這裡的人就更少了
who'd do it with their asses hanging out.
誰會在屁股懸著的情況下做這件事。
I'd like to add something to that.
我想補充一些內容。
What are you adding?
你要新增什麼？
Why are you adding?
為什麼要新增？
Most of you don't know me.
你們大多數人都不認識我。
I'm Rachel's boyfriend.
我是雷切爾的男朋友。
Oh, dear God.
哦，親愛的上帝。
Ross.
羅斯.
And I'd just like to say that it did take a lot of
我只想說這確實花了很多時間
courage for Rachel to come here tonight.
雷切爾今晚有勇氣來到這裡。
And just for the record, she did not run out on Barry because
鄭重宣告一下，她並沒有耗盡巴里的精力，因為
she had syphilis.
她患有梅毒。
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
I'm serious.
我是認真的。
The reason she walked out on Barry is simply that she didn't love
她離開巴里的原因很簡單，就是她不愛
him, which, incidentally, worked out pretty well for me.
順便說一句，這對我來說效果很好。
So, to review.
所以，要回顧一下。
Rachel took a lot of courage.
雷切爾需要很大的勇氣。
Doesn't have the syphilis.
沒有梅毒。
And wound up with me.
最後和我在一起了。
Cheers.
乾杯。
See you in the parking lot.
停車場見。
No, wait.
不，等等。
And once again, she is out of here, okay?
再一次，她要離開這裡，好嗎？
Who had 945, hmm?
誰有945，嗯？
You know what, Bear?
你知道嗎，小熊？
I'm not gonna leave.
我不會離開。
I probably should, but I'm not.
我可能應該這樣做，但我不是。
See, because I promised myself I would make it through at least one
看吧，因為我向自己保證我會至少透過一次
of your weddings.
你的婚禮。
See, now, tonight, all I really wanted was to make it through this
瞧，現在，今晚，我真正想要的就是度過這個難關
evening with a little bit of grace and dignity.
晚上帶著一點優雅和尊嚴。
Well, I guess we can all agree that's not gonna happen.
好吧，我想我們都同意這不會發生。
I guess there's nothing really left to say.
我想其實沒什麼好說的了。
Except, um...
除了，嗯...
Her name was Lola.
她的名字叫洛拉。
She was a showgirl.
她是一名歌舞女郎。
With yellow feathers in her hair And a dress cut down to there
她的頭髮上插著黃色的羽毛，還有一件剪裁得恰到好處的裙子
She would...
她會...
Meringue, hey, Meringue!
酥皮，嘿，酥皮！
And do the cha-cha And while she liked to be a star
跳恰恰舞 雖然她喜歡當明星
Tony always tended bar Wait, wait, everybody!
東尼總是照顧酒吧等等，等等，大家！
Lola Koba Koba Cabana Koba Cabana And Lola Koba
洛拉·科巴·科巴小屋 科巴小屋和洛拉·科巴
Cabana Used to get fashion We're always in fashion at the Koba There's
Cabana 曾經引領時尚 我們在 Koba 總是引領時尚
a somebody at the Koba Okay, I'll do it.
Koba 的某個人 好的，我會做的。
You'll do what?
你會做什麼？
If kids is what it takes to be with you, then kids it
is.
是。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Well, if I have to, I'll do it all again.
好吧，如果有必要的話，我會再做一次。
I'll do the four o'clock feeding thing.
我會做四點鐘餵食的事情。
I'll go to the PTA meetings.
我會去參加 PTA 會議。
I'll coach the soccer team.
我將擔任足球隊的教練。
Really?
真的嗎？
Yeah, if I have to.
是的，如果我必須的話。
Monica...
莫妮卡...
I don't want to lose you.
我不想失去你。
So if I have to do it all again, then I will.
因此，如果我必須重來一次，那麼我會的。
You're the most wonderful man.
你是最棒的男人。
And if you hadn't have said, If I have to, like 17 times,
如果你沒有說過「如果我必須這樣做」大概17次，
then I'd be saying, Okay, let's do it.
然後我會說，好吧，讓我們開始吧。
But you're not.
但你不是。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I can't believe what I'm getting ready to say.
我簡直不敢相信我正準備要說的話。
I want to have a baby.
我想要一個孩子。
But I don't want to have one with someone who doesn't really want
但我不想跟一個不真正想要的人在一起
to have one.
擁有一個。
I...
我...
I love you.
我愛你。
No, you do.
不，你知道。
You do.
你做。
So what now?
那現在怎麼辦？
I guess we just...
我想我們只是...
keep dancing.
繼續跳舞。
Someone to want to hold me.
有人想抱我。
Where is she?
她在哪裡？
Oh, hey, I have a question.
哦，嘿，我有一個問題。
Where is she?
她在哪裡？
Chandler, relax.
錢德勒，放鬆點。
Chandler shall be here.
錢德勒會在這裡。
Oh, oh, oh, that's her.
噢噢噢，就是她。
Yeah, because life's just that kind.
是的，因為生活就是這樣。
Chandler, you got to stop staring at the door.
錢德，你不能再盯著門看。
It's like a watched pot.
就像一個被監視的鍋子。
You know, if you keep looking at it, then the door is never
你知道，如果你一直看著它，那麼門永遠不會
going to boil.
快要沸騰了。
I think what you have to do is try not to...
我認為你要做的就是盡量不要...
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh...
哦...
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I've been feeling incredibly guilty about this because I want to be a
我對此感到非常內疚，因為我想成為一名
good friend, and damn it, I am a good friend, so just shut
好朋友，該死，我是個好朋友，所以就閉嘴吧
up and close your eyes.
站起來並閉上眼睛。
Wow.
哇。
You are a good friend.
你是一個好朋友。
Plus, the audition was this morning, and I didn't get it.
另外，今天早上試鏡，我沒有透過。
But that was a hell of a kiss.
但那是一個地獄般的吻。
Rachel is a very lucky girl.
雷切爾是個非常幸運的女孩。